<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="no_help_available">
      There is no help available at this time.
    </string>
    <string name="about_help_topics">
      Help is available for each section of this app.
    </string>

    <string name="help_page_intro">For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below.</string>
    <string name="help_page_intro_html">
    <![CDATA[
      For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below:
       ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section1">About</string>
    <string name="help_text_section1">
    This is the introduction of this application
    </string>
    <string name="help_topic_about">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        <b style="color:#000">
        	<p> <b style="color:#00FF"> Athlete Tracker Version 1.5.5 </b> </p>
	 		Athlete Tracker is an app which athlete can attach a phone to their body
		    and via GPS, track the location of the athlete, the distance they have run, 
		    the number of sprints above certain thresholds  
	    </b>
      </p>
      <p>
      	<b style="color:#000">
	         Application can show where player during the game, the run he made,
	         the sprints he made and essential "map" the movement of the player during
	         the game. Therefore, the player or coach can analyse where the player spent
	         most of his time, where he produced sprints
	     </b>
      </p>    
      <p>     
      </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
      ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section2">Required</string>
    <string name="help_text_section2">
     Hardware required to use this application
    </string>
    <string name="help_topic_require">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        This app required device must have GPS service and Internet connection
      </p>
      <p> 
       For Athlete Tracker to correctly track your progress, you need to be outdoors.
       The accuracy of this app base on the accuracy of GPS device.
      </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="help_title_section3">Guides</string>
    <string name="help_text_section3">
     Show you step-by-steps instruction to use this app
    </string>
    <string name="help_topic_guide">
    <![CDATA[
     
	 <p> 
      Enable <strong>GPS</strong> setting before starting application. </p>
	<p>Click <strong>Setting</strong> icon to adjust the <strong>Threshold</strong>. There are 4 Thresholds you can adjust</p>
	<p>Click Menu icon on Action bar to select various function of this app. </p>
	      <p> 
	      Click <strong>Start</strong> button on main screen to start tracking. Application will display the &quot;heat map&quot; of the player, the runs and the sprints which player has made</p>
	      <p>Click <strong>Pause</strong> button to pause tracking. </p>
	      <p>Click <strong>Stop</strong> button to stop tracking. </p>      
	       <p> 
	       After finish the tracking, the player information could be shared on Facebook
	       or upload to server.</p>
	      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
	</p>
       ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section4">Contacts</string>
    <string name="help_text_section4">
      Contact me
    </string>
    <string name="help_topic_contact">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
     	Contact to developer
      </p>
      <p> 
        If you have any question, please contact me via email
        <a href="tracker.support@raditel.net">tracker.support@raditel.net</a>. 
        Your ideas help me to create the better application
      </p>
      <p> 
      </p>
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
